Francesco Spata

Full Stack Engineer

I am currently pursuing my career as a software developer, thanks to the specialized training received through the progetto CODE and Codecademy. This path has prepared me for a professional role in this sector after obtaining a Bachelor's degree in Political Science, a significant milestone achieved following several years of work experience in other fields. In the future, I aspire to continue developing my skills in Web Development and explore new opportunities that allow me to grow both professionally and personally.

CONTACTS

franc.spata@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/francesco-spata

+39 392 6648869

SKILLS

- TypeScript, Next.js, React, Node.js, MySQL
- Git, GitHub
- Online content evaluation and indexing
- Italian native, English C1

EDUCATION

Università degli studi di Catania

Bachelor's degree in Political Science (2019 - 2023)

Specialization Course MSU

Michigan State University - Scholarship (2020 - 2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Engineer

2023 - Present

- Professional diploma
 Codecademy
- Professional diploma STEVE JOBS
 ACADEMY and progetto CODE

ADS Rater

2022 - 06/2024

TELUS INTERNATIONAL, Google Partner

- Daily work analyzing user query data for Google and evaluating advertisements.
- Building daily schedules independently and coordinating with teams.

Bartender

2016 - 2023

- Extensive experience in team work and shift work.
- Excellent public relations skills